Okay, let's do the same thing we did for
好 我们现在来做一件和感知算法一样的事情
the perception algorithm except now we're going to do it with this SVM algorithm.
但这次 我们要用到支持向量机算法
So, we start by looking at this set of points:
首先 我们来看一下这些点
blue and red and the line that separates them.
蓝点 红点 以及分开它们的这条线
And let's recall that the equation of the line is Wx + b = 0.
我们回想一下 这条线的方程是 Wx+b=0
But now we don't just want the line.
但现在我们想要的不止是这条线
We want the line with two extra lines that create the margin.
我们想要在这条线两侧再加两条线 形成间隔
And the equations for these lines are going to be Wx + b = 1 and Wx + b = -1.
这两条线的方程就是 Wx+b=1 和 Wx+b=-1
So, let's recall that we still want to punish the points that are incorrectly classified.
我们仍旧想要惩罚这些没有正确分类的点
But now, we're going to think of this region as points that are incorrectly
但现在 我们要把这个区域看做误分类的点
classified since we don't want anything in between these two lines.
因为我们不希望这两条线之间有任何东西
So, let's remember that and once again let's split the error in two.
记住这一点 我们再次把误差一分为二
So, we have the blue error except that now the blue error will
那么 我们有了蓝色误差 但现在的蓝色误差是从
start from the bottom line because we want to punish the points in the boundary too.
下面这条线开始的 因为我们也要惩罚间隔里的点
And our new red error is going to start in
而红色误差将从上面这条线开始
the top line because again we really want to punish the points in the boundary.
同样因为我们要惩罚间隔区域里面的点
So, let's split them like we did before and as I said,
像之前一样将它们分开 正如我所说的
the blue error starts from the bottom line and the red error
蓝色误差从底线开始 而红色误差
starts from the top line and we're going to do something very similar.
从顶线开始 接下来和之前一样
We look at the values of Wx + b.
我们来看 wx+b 的值
So, in the main line the value of Wx + b = 0.
在主线上 Wx+b 等于 0
And as we go up, it's going to be one, two, three, four, et cetera.
慢慢往上 Wx+b 就等于 1 2 3 4 等
And as we go down,
慢慢往下
it's going to be minus one, minus two,
Wx+b 就等于 -1 -2
minus three, et cetera..
-3 等
So, in order to build the error,
为了建立误差
we just take the absolute value of this and translated by one.
我们选取它的绝对值 即 1
So the blue error is going to start at zero on
那么 蓝色误差从底线开始就是 0
the bottom boundary line and then increase by one to get one, two, three, four,
慢慢增加为 1 2 3 4 等
et cetera.. And similarly,
同样的
the red error is going to be zero on
红色误差从顶线开始也是 0
top boundary line and then increase linearly in the opposite direction one,
往下逐渐反方向递减为 1
two, three, four, et cetera.
2 3 4 等
So, as we can see, there are three red points that give us
我们可以看到 蓝色区域内有三个红点
a blue error and notice that two of them are inside the margin,
并且其中两个处在间隔内
and there are three blue points that give us an error.
红色区域内有三个蓝点
These errors are given by the value on the side so it's 3.5 here,
它们的值分别为 3.5
1.5 here and 0.5 here.
1.5 和 0.5
And the errors on the right are two, three and 0.3.
右边的误差分别是 2 3 和 0.3
So, what we do is we just add these values and obtain the error.
我们需要做的就是把这些值加起来 得到误差
So, the error here would be 10.8 and in a nutshell,
那么 这里的误差是 10.8 简言之
that is a classification error for support vector machines.
这就是支持向量机的分类误差